Finding aid to the Classes of 1879-1890 records CA.MS.01023
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1887 Records, 1883-1961; 4 boxes (2.5 linear feet)
  - Class of 1887: Commencement Music (Box 1435, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1887: Commencement Speaker (Box 1435, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1887: Groups, 1886-87; undated (Box 1435, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1887: History, undated (Box 1435, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1887: Ivy Day (Box 1435, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1887: Class Letters, 1943-45 (Box 1435, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1887: Junior Banquet, 1886 (Box 1435, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1887: Junior Prom, 1886 (Box 1435, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1887: Reunions, 1912; 1932; 1937; 1942; 1947 (Box 1435, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1887: Senior Dramatics (Box 1435, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1887: Senior Questionnaire (Box 1435, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1887: Sophomore May Breakfast for 1885 (Box 1435, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1887: Sophomore Reception, 1883 (Box 1435, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1887: Class Supper (Box 1435, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1887: Bancroft, Antoinette Louise (Photographs, etc), 1883; 1885; undated (Box 1436, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1887: Bigelow, Jessie Elizabeth (Photographs, etc), 1886; 1938; undated (Box 1436, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1887: Bliss, Annie Louise, 1954; undated (Box 1436, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1887: Bodman, Rosa Maria (Photographs), undated (Box 1436, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1887: Bowles, Ruth Standish (Box 1436, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1887: Brown, Mabel (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1436, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1887: Carter, Jessie (Photographs, etc), 1889; undated (Box 1436, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1887: Caverno, Julia Harwood (Box 1436, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1887: Clark, Hannah Belle, 1887-88 (Box 1436, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1887: Crew, Caroline Ladd, 1903; 1961 (Box 1436, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1887: Day, Carrie Elizabeth (Photographs, etc), 1883-87; undated (Box 1436, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1887: Day, Carrie Elizabeth (Scrapbook) (Box 1436.1)
  - Class of 1887: Day, Harriet Green (Photographs, etc), 1886 (Box 1436, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1887: Fay, Lillian Watkins (Photographs), 1886; undated (Box 1436, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1887: Foskett, Mary Page (Photographs), 1885; undated (Box 1436, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1887: Gale, Alice (Letters), 1885-87; 1890-91; undated (Box 1436, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1887: Gale, Alice (Photographs), undated (Box 1436, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1887: Gale, Alice (Scrapbook) (Box 1436.2)
  - Class of 1887: Gamwell, Helen Lincoln (Photographs) (Box 1436, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1887: Giles, Anne Harper (Photographs), undated (Box 1436, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1887: Gill, Bessie Faunce (Photographs, etc), 1997; undated (Box 1436, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1887: Hager, Mary Earle (Photographs) (Box 1436, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1887: Holmes, Helen, undated (Box 1436, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1887: Hough, Celeste Frances (Photographs), undated (Box 1436, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1887: Hubbard, Alice J. (Photographs), undated (Box 1436, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1887: Hubbard, Grace A., undated (Box 1436, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1887: Hubbell, Clara Marvin, undated (Box 1436, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1887: James, Grace Fairchild, 1889; undated (Box 1436, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1887: James, Grace Fidelia (Photographs), undated (Box 1436, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1887: Leavens, Sarah Hall (Photographs), undated (Box 1436, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1887: Lewis, Maria Anna (Photographs), undated (Box 1436, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1887: Lord, Eleanor Louisa (Box 1436, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1887: Luce, Maud Lilian (Photographs) (Box 1436, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1887: Mason, Elizabeth Spauldiing (Box 1436, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1887: Parker, Emma Harriet (Photographs), 1886-87; undated (Box 1436, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1887: Pinkerton, Elizabeth Downing (Photographs), undated (Box 1436, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1887: Pinkerton (Scrapbook), Various dates (Box 1437)
  - Class of 1887: Porter, Allie Williams (spec.) (Photographs), undated (Box 1436, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1887: Reed, Clara Melinda, undated (Box 1436.1, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1887: Shaw, Adele Marie, 1941; undated (Box 1436.1, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1887: Shaw, Adele Marie (Writings), 1900; 1903-13 (Box 1436.1, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1887: Shute, Helen Winifred (Box 1436.1, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1887: Shute, Mary Appleton (Box 1436.1, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1887: Smith, Antoinette Julia (Photographs), undated (Box 1436.1, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1887: Van Kirk, Anne Dravo (Photographs, etc), 1948; undated (Box 1436.1, Folder 42)
  - Class of 1887: Walker, Emma E., 1883; 1885-86; 1954; undated (Box 1436.1, Folder 43)
  - Class of 1887: Walton, Mary Alice (Photographs, etc), 1918; undated (Box 1436.1, Folder 44)
  - Class of 1887: Webber, Lucie, undated (Box 1436.1, Folder 45)
  - Class of 1887: Williams, Clara Louise, 1885 (Box 1436.1, Folder 46)
  - Class of 1887: Woodhull, Marianna, 1915-16; undated (Box 1436.1, Folder 47)
  - Class of 1887: Woodruff, Martha Charlieana (Photographs, etc), 1949-50; undated (Box 1436.1, Folder 48)
  - Class of 1887: Woodruff, Martha Charlieana (Autograph Album, Photo Album), Various dates (Box 1438)
  - Class of 1887: Wright, Marion Adams (Box 1436.1, Folder 49)
- Class of 1888 Records, 1870-1958; 8 boxes (3.25 linear feet)
  The Class of 1888 was the tenth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1888 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1888. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, class letters, class notes, scrapbook, publications, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1888.
  - Class of 1888: Baccalaureate (Box 1439, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1888: Class Letters (Box 1439, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1888: Commencement (Box 1439, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1888: Commencement Music (Box 1439, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1888: Groups, 1884-85; undated (Box 1439, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1888: Ivy Day (Box 1439, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1888: Junior Prom, 1887 (Box 1439, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1888: Reunions 1903, 1908 (Box 1439, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1888: Reunions 1913 (Box 1439, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1888: Reunions 1923 (Box 1439, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1888: Reunions 1928 (Box 1439, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1888: Reunions 1933 (Box 1439, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1888: Reunions 1938 (Box 1439, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1888: Reunions 1948, 1958 (Box 1439, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1888: Reunion Songs, 1923; 1938 (Box 1439, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1888: Senior Dramatics (Box 1439, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1888: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) (Box 1439, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1888: Senior Parties (Box 1439, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1888: Songs, 1923; 1948 (Box 1439, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1888: Sophomore Reception, 1884 (Box 1439, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1888: Class Supper (Box 1439, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1888: Class Letters, 1888-1907 (Box 1440)
  - Class of 1888: Class Letters, 1908-1934 (Box 1441)
  - Class of 1888: Class Letters, 1935-1953 (Box 1442)
  - Class of 1888: Austin, Caroline Sprague (Photographs), undated (Box 1443, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1888: Bailey, Florence Kate (Photographs) (Box 1443, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1888: Barton, Minerva May (Photographs), undated (Box 1443, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1888: Benson, Sarah Louise (Photographs), undated (Box 1443, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1888: Blaisdell, Daisy Luana, undated (Box 1443, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1888: Boardman, Harriette Holland, undated (Box 1443, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1888: Bosworth, Susie Belle (Photographs, etc), 1934 (Box 1443, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1888: Brooks, Lucy Bagg (Photographs, etc), 1886; undated (Box 1443, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1888: Brown, Adelaide, 1925; 1935; 1937-39; 1941 (Box 1443, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1888: Brown, Adelaide (Scrapbook regarding honorary degree), 1939 (Box 1443, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1888: Burrington, Grace Alice (Photographs), undated (Box 1443, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1888: Carter, Anna Louise (Photographs), undated (Box 1443, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1888: Chamberlain, Jennie (Photographs, etc), 1913; 1948; undated (Box 1443, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1888: Chandler, Belle (Photographs), undated (Box 1443, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1888: Chase, Mabelle (Photographs), undated (Box 1443, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1888: Church, Cornelia Chapell (Photographs), undated (Box 1443, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1888: Churchyard, Grace (Letters, etc), 1885; 1912; 1914; 1931; undated (Box 1443, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1888: Churchyard, Grace (Publications), 1910-1913; undated (Box 1443, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1888: Cobb, Mary Esther, 1926; 1929; 1954; 1958; 1992; undated (Box 1443, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1888: Cobb, Mary Esther, 1992 (Box 1443, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1888: Cobb, Mary Esther (Poems), 1992 (Box 1443, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1888: De Vol, Mary Frances (Photographs), undated (Box 1443, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1888: Dewey, Mary, undated (Box 1443, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1888: Du Bois, Lilian (Photographs, etc), 1911; undated (Box 1443, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1888: Duguid, Harriet Eliza (Photographs), undated (Box 1443, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1888: Dwight, Marion McGregor (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1443, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1888: Eaton, Isabel (Photographs, etc), 1913; undated (Box 1443, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1888: Everett, Martha Elizabeth (Photographs, etc), 1884; 1887; 1908; 1921-24; 1928-29; 1933-35; 1943; 1948; undated (Box 1444, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1888: French, Isabella (Photographs), 1886; undated (Box 1444, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1888: Gardner, Anna Warren (Photographs), undated (Box 1444, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1888: Gower, Katy Helen (Photographs), 1903 (Box 1444, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1888: Guild, Lora Elsine (Photographs), undated (Box 1444, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1888: Hall, Sarah Mabel, 1870; 1884-85; 1927; 1939; undated (Box 1444, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1888: Hardy, Fannie Pearson (Photographs, etc), 1893-94; 1902; 1904; 1908; 1911; 1914; 1924; 1939-40; 1947; 1949; 1953; 1977-78; 1983; undated (Box 1444, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1888: Hawker, Annah Dora (Photographs), undated (Box 1444, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1888: Husted, Louise Akerly (Photographs), undated (Box 1444, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1888: Jameson, Caroline Cogswell (Photographs), undated (Box 1444, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1888: Kellogg, Annie Prindle (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1444, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1888: Kelly, Jane Downes, 1938; 1950 (Box 1444, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1888: Kelly, Jane Downes (Photographs), undated (Box 1444, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1888: Kennedy, Leila Mantha (Photographs), undated (Box 1444, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1888: Leonard, Florence, 1890 (Box 1445, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1888: Lincoln, Helen Stoddard (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1888: Lord, Mary Caroline (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1888: Lyman, Frances Pease (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1888: Mather, Lucy Olcott (Photographs) (Box 1445, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1888: Nichols, May Louise (Photographs, etc), 1902; 1905; 1912; 1924; 1948 (Box 1445, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1888: Packard, Grace Sophronia, undated (Box 1445, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1888: Parker, Lizzie S. (Letters), 1884; 1887-88; 1893; 2001; undated (Box 1445, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1888: Parker, Lizzie Southgate (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1888: Parker, Lizzie Southgate (Class notes, Scrapbook), Various dates (Box 1446)
  - Class of 1888: Plack, Martha Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1888: Raymer, Mary Balmer, undated (Box 1445, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1888: Robinson, Alice, undated (Box 1445, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1888: Schreuder, Anna Ellen (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1888: Seelye, Harriet Chapin (Box 1445, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1888: Shevelson, Rachel (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1888: Skilton, Alice Thomas (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1888: Sykes, Alice May, undated (Box 1445, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1888: Thompson, Mary Frances (Photographs, etc), 1888-89 (Box 1445, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1888: Twitchell, Susie H. (Letters), 1886-87 (Box 1445, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1888: Twitchell, Susie Helen (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1888: Ventres, Adelaide Brainerd (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1888: Weeks, Katharine Ellen (Photographs), 1884; undated (Box 1445, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1888: Wentworth, Ellen Lang (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1888: Whitney, Margaret Olive (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1888: Wilcoxen, Jennie Sarah (Photographs), undated (Box 1445, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1888: Willard, Mary Randall, undated (Box 1445, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1888: Woodruff, Mary Alvira, 1907 (Box 1445, Folder 27)
- Class of 1889 Records, 1868-1954; 4 boxes (1 linear ft. and 8 linear inches)
  The Class of 1889 was the eleventh graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1889 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1889. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, publications, course notes, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1889.
  - Class of 1889: Baccalaureate Service (Box 1447, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1889: Commencement (Box 1447, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1889: Commencement Music (Box 1447, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1889: Farewell Party (Box 1447, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1889: Groups, 1885-89 (Box 1447, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1889: History, undated (Box 1447, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1889: Ivy Day (Box 1447, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1889: Junior Prom, 1888 (Box 1447, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1889: Class Letters, 1890; 1919-20; 1930; 1932-35 (Box 1447, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1889: Organization, 1885-1929 (Box 1447, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1889: Class Photo Book (Box 1447, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1889: Reunions, 1890 (Box 1447, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs, undated (Box 1447, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs, 1914 (Box 1447, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs, 1919 (Box 1447, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs, 1924 (Box 1447, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs, 1934 (Box 1447, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs, 1939 (Box 1447, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs, 1949 (Box 1447, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1889: Reunion Photographs, 1954 (Box 1447, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1889: Songs, undated (Box 1447, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1889: Sophomore Reception, 1886 (Box 1447, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1889: Class Supper (Box 1447, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1889: Senior Dramatics (Box 1448, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1889: Senior Dramatics ("Electra" Manuscript Book) (Box 1448, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1889: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) (Box 1448, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1889: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) (Box 1448, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1889: Composite (Box 1449, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1889: Abbot, Ella Caroline (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1449, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1889: Allen, Lucy Ellis (Photographs, etc), undated (Box 1449, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1889: Atwater, Elsie Welling (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1889: Blake, Jennie Maria, 1886; undated (Box 1449, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1889: Blinn, Harriet Louise, undated (Box 1449, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1889: Blodgett, Grace Allen, undated (Box 1449, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1889: Buell, Gertrude Frances, undated (Box 1449, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1889: Buswell, Alice Maud (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1889: Carr, Agnes (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1889: Cobb, Harriet Redfield (Box 1449, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1889: Colgan, Mary Ella (Photographs, etc), 1914 (Box 1449, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1889: Cullinan, Catherine (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1889: Cushing, Jane Delia (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1889: Davis, Grace Gilbert, undated (Box 1449, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1889: Deane, Harriet Robinson, undated (Box 1449, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1889: Dickinson, Martha Gilbert, 1892; 1898; 1900-01; 1908-10; 1915 (Box 1449, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1889: Doane, Caroline Ida (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1889: Fiske, Ida Mabel, undated (Box 1449, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1889: Fletcher, Mabel (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1889: Gale, Anna (Photographs, etc), 1886-87; 1890; undated (Box 1449, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1889: Gaylord, Mary Foster (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1889: Gere, Mary Elizabeth, undated (Box 1449, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1889: Gilmour, Anna Catherine (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1889: Goodwin, May Amelia (Photographs, etc), 1889-92; 1896; 1898; 1900; 1903; undated (Box 1449, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1889: Gray, Nellie, undated (Box 1449, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1889: Hastings, Caroline Ella, undated (Box 1449, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1889: Hazen, Emily (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1889: Hopkins, Martha Austin (Photographs, etc), 1885-87; undated (Box 1449, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1889: Johnson, Alice Robinson (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1889: Johnson, Alice Robbins, undated (Box 1449, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1889: Knowles, Jane Sherrill (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1889: Lovejoy, Margaret Waldo, 1922; 1982; 1998; undated (Box 1449, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1889: Loveland, Helen Isabella, undated (Box 1449, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1889: Mason, Mary Arlina (Photographs), 1902; undated (Box 1449, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1889: Moore, Julia Harrison (Photographs), undated (Box 1449, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1889: Newland, Sarah Luella (Photographs), undated (Box 1450, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1889: Paine, Elizabeth Elmore (Photographs, etc), 1868; 1884-89; 1891; 1925; undated (Box 1450, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1889: Parker, Harriet Eliza, 1896; 1908-09; 1913; 1930; 1932; 1934-42; 1945-47 (Box 1450, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1889: Peirce, Eliza Metcalf, undated (Box 1450, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1889: Read, Marion Pugh, 1914-15; 1921 (Box 1450, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1889: Reed, Theodora Williams, undated (Box 1450, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1889: Rich, Ruby Lucy, 1885-87; 1893; undated (Box 1450, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1889: Rich, Ruby Lucy (Course notes, Bible), 1888 (Box 1450, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1889: Rich, Ruby Lucy (Course notes, Bible), 1885 (Box 1450, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1889: Robinson, Harriet Marcia (Box 1450, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1889: Scribner, Eleanor, undated (Box 1450, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1889: Seaver, Florence White (Photographs, etc), 1886-87; 1893; 1947; undated (Box 1450, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1889: Sebring, Emma Goodeve, 1923; 1925; 1983 (Box 1450, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1889: Seelye, Abigail Taylor, 1895; undated (Box 1450, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1889: Seelye, Anna Hawley, 1896; undated (Box 1450, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1889: Shepard, Anna North (Photographs), 1888 (Box 1450, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1889: Swan, Almira French, undated (Box 1450, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1889: Symmes, Frances Newton, 1888; 1890; undated (Box 1450, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1889: Taylor, Alice Stanley (Photographs), 1888; undated (Box 1450, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1889: Taylor, Elizabeth Davenport, 1887 (Box 1450, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1889: Thayer, Mary S., undated (Box 1450, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1889: Thompson, Annie Maynard, 1935 (Box 1450, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1889: Tilton, Mary Susan (Photographs), undated (Box 1450, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1889: Trow, Mary Elizabeth (Photographs), undated (Box 1450, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1889: Washburn, Mary Nightingale (Photographs), undated (Box 1450, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1889: Washburn, Mary N. (Sketch book), 1880 (Box 1450, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1889: White, Grace Grosvenor, 1918; 1925; undated (Box 1450, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1889: Whitfield, Inez Harrington (Photographs, etc), 1929; undated (Box 1450, Folder 28)
- Class of 1890 Records, 1886-1975; 4 boxes (1 linear ft. and 8 linear inches)
  The Class of 1890 was the twelfth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1890 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1890. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, publications, questionnaires, class records, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1890.
  - Class of 1890: Baccalaureate (Box 1451, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1890: Commencement (Box 1451, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1890: Commencement Music (Box 1451, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1890: Commencement Speaker (Box 1451, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1890: Freshman Grind by 1889, 1886 (Box 1451, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1890: Groups, 1886-89 (Box 1451, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1890: Groups (Unidentified groups and individuals), 1887-88; undated (Box 1451, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1890: Ivy Day (Box 1451, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1890: Junior Prom, 1889 (Box 1451, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1890: Officers, 1886-90; 1892; 1895; 1900; 1905; 1910; 1915; 1920; 1925; 1930; 1935; 1940; 1948 (Box 1451, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1890: Class Photo Book (Box 1451, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1890: Questionnaires, Reunion 1920 (Originals) (Box 1451, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1890: Questionnaires, Reunion 1920 (Copies) (Box 1451, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1890: Questionnaires, 1950? (Box 1451, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1890: Class Letters, 1891-1940 (Box 1451, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1890: Smith Quarterly (Book), 1930-1940 (Box 1452)
  - Class of 1890: Class Records (Book), 1886-90; 1892; 1895; 1900; 1905; 1910; 1915; 1920; 1925; 1930; 1935; 1940 (Box 1452)
  - Class of 1890: Class Records, 1948-56; 1958-61 (Box 1452, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1890: Reunion, 1910 (Box 1452, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1890: Reunion, 1920 (Box 1452, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1890: Reunion, 1925 (Box 1452, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1890: Reunion, 1930 (Box 1452, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1890: Reunion, 1940; 1950 (Box 1452, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1890: Reunion, 1945 (Box 1452, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1890: Reunion Photographs, 1905?; 1910?; 1940; 1950 (Box 1452, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1890: Senior Dramatics ("Book of Job"- Music) (Box 1452, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1890: Senior Dramatics ("Book of Job"- Programs, Review) (Box 1452, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1890: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) (Box 1452, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1890: Songs, undated (Box 1452, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1890: Sophomore Reception, 1886 (Box 1452, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1890: Class Supper (Box 1452, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1890: Allen, Adaline White (Photographs, etc), 1941; undated (Box 1453, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1890: Barton, Alice, 1944-45 (Box 1453, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1890: Blodgett, Mattie Bacon, 1893 (Box 1453, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1890: Booth, Minnie Day (Photographs), undated (Box 1453, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1890: Bowen, Fanny Corey (Photographs), undated (Box 1453, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1890: Brown, Clara May (Photographs) (Box 1453, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1890: Bufkin, Mary L., undated (Box 1453, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1890: Burnham, Jessica (Photographs), 1886; 1896; 1900; 1966; undated (Box 1453, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1890: Carpenter, Mary Frances (Scrapbook), Various dates (Box 1453, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1890: Cate, Carrie Quincy, 1942 (Box 1453, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1890: Cheever, Louisa Sewall (Box 1453, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1890: Clark, Abigail Hinsdale, 1945 (Box 1453, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1890: Crandall, Regina Katharine, 1891; 1940; undated (Box 1453, Folder 13)